Guide to the Ted Fagan Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Ted Fagan's Writting
  - Research papers
    - One and only Electra. Commentary on Sartre's les Mouches (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Existentialism. Jean Paul Sartre (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - The literary artistry of Jean Paul Sartre (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Dostoyevsky's Philosophy (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Rupert Brooke (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Personal
    - Hundred pages and later. 1946 - (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Life in New York and travel to Santiago, Chile (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous writings from 1948 to 1979 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Diaries starting in 1979 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Fragments (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Official Documents
  - Fagan's Argentinian passport (1930); civilian (1935) and military (1943) identification cards (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Fagan's court interpreter certificate1980 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - United Nations identification cards (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Fagan's school grades1936 and 1939 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Family documents (Box 54, Folder 5)
    British Passport (1957): Fagan's father, Alfred Frank Fagin; Death certificate (1953): Fagan's mother, Rebecca Fagin
- Correspondence
  - 1946-1948 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - 1950-1985 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Recruitment and training of interpreters (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - GEMS (Box 50, Folder 4)
- United Nations Materials
  - Nürnberg Trials1946 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Visit of Pope Paul VI to the UNOct. 1965 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Castro Fidel, letter and Chile and the Junta (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Conferencia. Derecho del Mar. Caracas, Venezuela 1974 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Castro, Fidel address to the non alined countriesMarch 20, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Conference on alternative strategies for desert development and management1977 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Conferencia de jefes de estado o de gobierno de países no-alineados. Cuba1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Comité International Olympique. Commissopm exécutive. Los AngelesFeb. 3-5, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - On interpreting (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Concerning interpreters (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Discourse. San Francisco (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Political materials (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Publicity1947 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Publicity1948 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Fagan's Memoirs on the UN (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Fagan on UN policies (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Fagan on political issues (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Personal I - Contracts, reports, official memos (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Personal II - Contracts, reports, official memos (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - UN Miscellaneous documents (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - UN related invitations (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - UN Publications I (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - UN Publications II - Secretariat News 1959 - 1977 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - UN Reports I (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - UN Reports II (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - UN Reports III (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - UN Reports IV (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - UN Testimonial to Ted FaganOct. 24, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Computer Diskettes of Fagan's book on the UN (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Photographs filed with UN honorary document (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Photographs (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Annotated Books
  - Titta Ruffo. An Anthology. Frakas, Andrew, editor (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Tibbett, Lawrence. Glory Road. An Autobiography (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Kenn. Ultimate opera quiz book (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Societá Italiana di Fonotipia. Milano1953 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Koenigsberg, Allen. Edison Cylinder Records, 1889-1912 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1923-. Pure Contraption, Hard cover book (Box 53, Folder 6)
    With autograph
  - Rorem, Ned, 1923-. Pure Contraption, Hard cover book (Box 53, Folder 7)
    With dedication: to Ted Fagan with you can't be you' re [?] with something immortal. Ned Rorem, 1967
- Miscellaneous
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Pages Romantiques, Photocopies of a book (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - On French stage music, Photocopies of several secondary sources (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Negatives. Garden and plants (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Frank, Miguel. Nunca como antes. Novela (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Letter by Goodman, Benny
  - American Esperanto MagazineMarch-April 1949 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Review of International Organizations and Meetings 1954 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - National Geographic. Issue dedicated to the United Nations1961 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Various documents (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Clippings
  - 1946-1948 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - 1949-1957 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - 1959-1973 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - 1974-1976 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - 1977-1980 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Undated (Box 55, Folder 7)